GREGORY A. AKHUN

After a medical career, I decided to embrace my passion which is web development. With my optimism and my good mood, I take every challenge as an experience. Always motivated to learn new technologies in order to master new front end and back end skills.

SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- JavaScript
- ReactJS / React Native
- Express.js
- Node.js
- REST API
- SQL / MySQL / Sequelize
- C#
- Java
- Material UI
- Git / Github
- Unity (game engine)
- Blender 3D
- Agile
- Figma / Trello
- Slack / Teams / Discord
- Salesforce (CRM)

LANGUAGES

- French: C2

- English : C1

HOBBIES

- Music
- Reading
- Travelling
- Video game
- Video game developement

CONTACT



(+32) 472 73 64 33



🔀 gregakhun@gmail.com



Greg155



in Gregory Alfonso Akhun

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER & MEDICAL BIOLOGY

EXPERIENCE

Full stack web developer

Wild Code School | Septembre 2020 to present

Scout 47: Soccer scouting application

· Created and designed a web and a mobile application solution to manage a soccer scouting team, base on real client need.

React/React Native/ Express.js / Node.js / CSS / MaterialUI / Sequelize

Explore-IT | City traveling app

 Developed a React app that allows travelers to discover a city through a quizz game.

React / CSS / Google Map API

Tech-IT-Easy | Tech landing page

 Create and design a landing page for a technological ecosystem start-up HTML / CSS / JavaScript

Peaky Prohibiton | Hackathon

• Create and design a whiskey e-commerce application under 36H to answer a challenging task. React / CSS

Application specialist in medical devices

Hitchi medical systems | March 2019 - September 2020

 Assist doctors to choose and set-up their ultrasound device(s) that fit their professional needs.

Lab technician in echocardiolog

Cliniques St Luc | October 2016 - February 2019

• Made echocardiography and report the results on the health of the patient's heart.

Internships in Haematology / Microbology / Neurochemistry / Immunology

from 1 to 3 months: 2015-2016

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

Wild Code School

Intensive training in full stack web development (6 months 2020-2021)

• 3 web developer projects in agile and 1 hackathon of 36 h

Bachelor degree in IT management

EPHEC / ICC (September 2018 - June 2022)

Bachelor degree in medical biology

Institut Paul Lambin (September 2013 - June 2016)

Bachelor in medecine

UCLouvain - Brussels (September 2011 - June 2013)

High school Graduate

European School of Brussels III (2011)

General science